// QuestionBank.js

const QuizData = [
	{
		id: 1,
		question: "ALU stands for ?",
		options: ["Algorithm and logical unit", "Arithmetic and logical unit", "Arithmetic and logarithm unit", "Algorithm and logarithm unit "],
		answer: 2,
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		question: "A group of ………………... is commonly called as one byte ?",
		options: ["Six bits", "Eight bits", "TEN Bits", "Nine bits"],
		answer: 2,
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		question:"The Fourth Generation Computer used ?" ,
		options: ["Microprocessor"," Transistors" ,"Integrated circuit", "Vacuum tube"],
		answer: 1,
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		question: "Who among the following has invented cut/copy and paste ? ",
		options: ["Ward Cunningham ","Larry Tesler ","Lee de Forest","Leonard Max Adleman"],
		answer:2,
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		question: "The 'P' in CPU stands for ?",
		options: ["Process","Program","Performance","Plan"],
		answer: 1,
	},
    {
        id:6,
        question:"The hardware in which data may be stored for a computer system is called ?",
        options:["Memory", "Control unit", "Bus","Register"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:"RAM chips?",
        options:["Store data indefinitely unless you delete it","Allow the computer to store data electronically","Are always measured in thousand of bytes","used to store data"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:"The CPU and memory are located on the ?",
        options:["Keyboard","Graphics board","Sound board", "Motherboard"],
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:"Which of the following manages computer resources ?",
        options:[ "BUS","ALU","I/O unit","Control unit"],
        answer: 4,
     },
     {
        id:10,
        question:"Speed of processor is measured in?",
        options:[ "Hertz","Pathom", "Byte","Bit"],
        answer:1,

     } 
]

export default QuizData;
